Panama
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Panama, 2.1.1.1.18
  - From controlling tower, gates and lighthouse at Gatún, 1913 September 7-9; 7; 1653; 42; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Walls of locks extending into Gatún Lake, 1913 September; 8; 1654; 43; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Upper locks looking toward Gatún Lake, 1913 September; 9; 1655; 44; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - On middle lock at Gatún, detail of gates, Frank R. Roberson on wood plank, 1913 September 7-9; 10; 1656; 45; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Middle lock, taken inside of lock, Gatún, 1913 September 7-9; 11; 1657; 46; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Detail view of middle lock gate at Gatún, 1913 September; 12; 1658; 47; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - The spillway at Gatún, from lake side, 1913 September; 13; 1659; 84; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Hook[?] to hold boats at side, inside of lock, Gatún, 1913 September 7-9; 14; 1660; 48; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Central wall and emergency dam at Pedro Miguel Lock, 1913 September 7-9; 15; 1662; 30X; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Emergency dam in use at Pedro Miguel Lock, 1913 September 7-9; 16; 1663; 51; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Testing the emergency dam at Pedro Miguel Lock, 1913 September; 17; 1664; 52; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Emergency dam at Pedro Miguel Lock, 1913 September; 18; 1665; 53; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Entrance to water conduits, Pedro Miguel Lock, 1913 September 7-9; 19; 1666; 54; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Cables on emergency dam in action, Pedro Miguel Lock, 1913 September 7-9; 20; 1667; 55; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Emergency dam showing method of working plates, Pedro Miguel Lock, 1913 September 7-9; 21; 1668; 56; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Working the plates of emergency dam, Pedro Miguel Lock, 1913 September; 22; 1669; 57; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Emergency dam, machinery working plates into position, Pedro Miguel Lock, 1913 September 7-9; 23; 1670; 58; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Miraflores Locks, side view, 1913 September 7-9; 24; 1671; 61; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Miraflores Dam, 1913 September 7-9; 25; 1672; 62; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Power plant at Miraflores, 1913 September; 26; 1673; 63; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Dam at Miraflores, 1913; 27; 1674; 64; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Miraflores Locks looking toward the Pacific, 1913; 28; 1675; 65; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Railroad station, city of Panama, 1913; 29; 1676; 66; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Culebra Cut, from bridge at Empire, 1913; 30; 1677; 67; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Upper Culebra Cut, from Empire bridge (upright), 1913 September 7-9; 31; 1678; 68; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - The cut at Empire, taken from bank, 1913; 32; 1679; 69; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Culebra Cut at Empire, 1913; 33; 1680; 70; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Cut at Empire, looking toward Pacific, 1913; 34; 1681; 71; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  Box 1228
- Panama, 2.1.1.1.18
  - Bridge at Empire, 1913 September 7-9; 1; 1682; 72; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Fire burning ties in cut at Empire, 1913 September 7-9; 2; 1684; 73; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Bridge at Empire, taken from bottom of cut, 1913; 3; 1685; 74; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Bonfire of railroad ties in cut at Empire, 1913 September 7-9; 4; 1686; 75; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Culebra Cut (used as a night picture, to be colored as a night picture, background dark purple, foreground a dark green, sky blue and silver gray), 1913 September 7-9; 5; 1687; 76; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Culebra Cut showing bonfire of railroad ties, 1913; 6; 1688; 77; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Colonel Siebert (or Sieber), 1913 September 7-9; 7; 1689; 78; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Two lower Gatún locks, taken from top lock, 1913 September 7-9; 8; 1690; 79; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Top lock and lake at Gatún, 1913 September 7-9; 9; 1691; 80; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Upper gates, middle lock, Gatún, looking into lock, 1913 September 7-9; 10; 1692; 81; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Two lower locks and Atlantic entrance, Gatún, 1913 September 7-9; 11; 1693; 82; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - The spillway at Gatún, Atlantic side, 1913 September; 12; 1694; 85; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - The spillway at Gatún showing baffle piers, 1913 September; 13; 1695; 86; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Showing towers of spillway, Gatún, 1913 September; 14; 1696; 87; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Detail of spillway, Atlantic side, Gatún, 1913 September; 15; 1697; 88; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Showing gates of the spillway, Gatún, 1913 September; 16; 1698; 89; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Looking toward Atlantic entrance from top of lower lock, Gatún, 1913 September; 17; 1699; 90; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Lower east side lock, Gatún, 1913 September 7-9; 18; 1700; 92; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Lower lock at Gatún, looking up, 1913 September; 19; 1701; 93; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Center retaining wall, lower lock at Gatún, 1913 September; 20; 1702; 94; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Showing small guard gate in lowest lock at Gatún, 1913 September; 21; 1703; 95; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Machinery working lock gates, Gatún, 1913 September; 22; 1704; 96; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Big axle of lock gates, 1913 September; 23; 1705; 97; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Gaus and Schumacher party at Gatún Locks, 1913 September; 24; 1706; 33; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Party on the emergency dam at Pedro Miguel, 1913 September 7-9; 25; 1707; 60; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Group on deck of the United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, with Captain Smith, 1913 September 7-9; 26; 1708; 2; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  - Through window of controlling tower, general view toward Atlantic, Gatún, 1913 September 7-9; 27; 1709; 41; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1228)
  Box 1229
- Panama, 2.1.1.1.18
  - Panama copies, circa 1912; 1; 204X-205X-206X-207X; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1229)
  - Panama copies, circa 1912; 2; 208X-209X-210X-211X; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1229)
  - Panama copies, circa 1912; 3; 212X-213X-214X-215X; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1229)
  - Panama copies, circa 1912; 4; 216X-217X; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1229)
  - Panama copies, circa 1912; 5; 218X-219X; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1229)
  - Panama copies, circa 1912; 6; 220X-221X; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1229)
  - Panama copies, circa 1912; 7; 222X-239X; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1229)
  - Panama copies, circa 1912; 8; 223X-224X-225X; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1229)
  - Panama copies, circa 1912; 9; 226X-227X-228X-229X; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1229)
  - Panama copies, circa 1912; 10; 230X-231X; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1229)
  - Panama copies, circa 1912; 11; 232X-233X; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1229)
  - Panama copies, circa 1912; 12; 234X-235X; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1229)
  - Panama copies, circa 1912; 13; 236X-237X-238X; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1229)